tradingconceptsinc.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Policy - Trading Concepts, Inc.

Your privacy is very important to us. We want to make your experience on the Internet as enjoyable and profitable as possible and want you to use the services and products we offer with complete confidence.

We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our commitment to privacy and security. This Privacy Policy describes how our company collects information from all the people who use our Internet services (the Services). Those who visit our site and may access some our Services without having accounts with us (Visitors) as well as those who purchase Products and pay a fee to subscribe to our Services (Members). It also sets out what we do with the information we collect and the choices Visitors and Members have concerning the collection and use of this information. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

## Personal Information Our Company  
Collects And How It Is Used

**Introduction** Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services on this or related web sites. We use this information mainly to provide a personalized experience as you use our Products and Services and generally do not share this information with third parties.

However, we may disclose personal information collected, if we have received your prior permission, or in very special circumstances as when we believe disclosure is required by law and in the special cases described below.

**What you provide and what we collect, store, and process** By clicking through to any Trading Concepts video or sales page, you grant Trading Concepts the right to collect your IP address and to store an MD5-hashed version. You also grant Trading Concepts permission to have Google Analytics collect and process your IP address, browser and operating system information, any cookies generated by a domain owned by Trading Concepts, and your interaction with the site. By submitting any personal information, you indicate that you are at least 18 years old. You also grant Trading Concepts the right to collect and to store your interaction and consumption of this video or sales page and to associate it with this MD5-hashed IP address. By submitting data, you grant Trading Concepts permission to have Infusionsoft store this data. You also grant Trading Concepts permission to log this data for the purposes of ensuring that your account is created and tagged accordingly. These logs should be stored on LiquidWeb Rackspace’s servers or on Lightning Base’s servers. Any credit card information you supply should be stored solely in Infusionsoft. To read more about Infusionsoft’s practices, please see https://www.infusionsoft.com/legal/dpa. You also grant Trading Concepts permission to track your consumption and interaction of content Trading Concepts provides, including when you click on our emails, submit our forms, the amount of our videos you watch, and what products you have purchased from us. Additionally, you consent to have Trading Concepts process this data to customize offers to you based on your past actions and to provide support for your account. Should you wish to delete or view your data, please contact our DPO (Data Protection Officer) directly at amy@tradingconceptsinc.com. 

**Upon Registration** Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our free content and Products and Services including name, address, telephone number, billing information, (such as credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. Personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Memberâ€™s account (such as for billing purposes.Â By providing your email address, you give and agree that you give explicit consent to receive commercial emails from Trading Concepts, whether sent directly from our own databases, a third-party sending an email on our behalf, or from any representative of our company. You may revoke this consent at any time by opting out of our communications. This information is not shared with third parties, except as specifically stated, as a way to facilitate an email send on our behalf, or in special circumstances, including but not limited to a third-party providing a service to Trading Concepts or a third-party in a separate domain that is shared with Trading Concepts.

However in instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner some personal information like the name, address and user name of the persons who subscribed who subscribed to the Services as a result of the joint promotion solely for the purpose of allowing us and the partner to asses the results of the promotion.

In this case, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. We may also generate general non-identifying profiles from personal information our Members provide during registration, (like total number, but not the names of Members). As explained below, we would use this information to sell advertisements which may appear in the Services.

**With Partners** Some Products and Services may be offered to Visitors and Members in conjunction with an affiliate, independent contract seller or non-affiliated partner. To provide Visitors and Members with some of these Products and Services, the partner may need to collect and maintain personal information. In such cases, you will be notified before any of your data is collected or transferred, giving you the choice of consent and allowing you to decide whether to use that particular feature or service.

**Shopping** If you order Products or Services from our company we will use the personal information you provide only to process the order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the order.

**Advertisements** Our company may display online advertisements. In those cases we share general non-identifying profile information about our Visitors and Members collected during the registration process as well as through online surveys and promotions with these advertisers.

In some cases, we use this general non-identifying profile information to deliver specific advertisements and for joint ventures. As an example, an advertiser or joint venture company tells us the audience they want to reach and provides us an advertisement tailored to the audience. Based upon the general non-identifying profile information we have collected, we may then display or send the information to the intended people. Our company does not share personal information of Visitors and Members with these advertisers or joint venture partners.

**Responses to Email Inquiries** When Visitors or Members send email inquiries to our company, the return email address is used to answer the email inquiry we receive. Our company does not use the return email address we receive for any other purpose and does not share the return email address with anyone else.

**Voluntary Customer Surveys** We may periodically conduct both business and individual customer surveys. We encourage our customers to participate in these surveys because they provide us with important information which helps us to improve the types of products and services we offer and how we provide them to you for your benefit. Your personal information and responses will remain strictly confidential, even if the survey is conducted by a third party. Participation in customer surveys is voluntary.

We may take the information we receive from people responding to our surveys and combine it with the responses of other customers we have to prepare broader, general responses to the survey questions (such as age, gender, residence, hobbies, education, employment, industry and other demographic information). We then use this information to improve the quality of the Services and Products we provide to you and to develop new products and services. This general non-identifying profile information may be shared with third parties.

**Special Cases** It is our companyâ€™s policy not to use or share the personal information we collect about Visitors and Members in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you the prior opportunity to opt out and prohibit such unrelated disclosures.

However we may disclose information about Visitors or Members, or information concerning your use of the Services and Products or Websites accessible through the use of our Services or Products for any reason, if in our sole discretion we feel it is reasonable to do so (as permitted by law were applicable) such as to credit agencies, collection agencies, law enforcement, to protect the interests of our Company and Members, or as required by law.

**â€œCookiesâ€** A â€œcookieâ€ is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain web sites.

**How We Use Cookies** Our company may use â€œcookiesâ€ to collect, store and track data for statistical purposes to improve the products and services we provide and to manage our networks.

If you are a Visitor or Member we may use cookies to save your settings and provide customized and personal service. These cookies do not allow any third parties to access any of your customer information. Advertisers and Partners may also use cookies. We have no control over their actions and we specifically disclaim any responsibility for information they may collect.

**Our Companyâ€™s policy towards child privacy** The privacy of children is important to all of us. To ensure compliance with any applicable children privacy laws we restrict our Web site to people 18 years of age or over.

You must be eighteen (18) years of age or over to access this web site. If you are under eighteen (18) years of age, you are not permitted to access this web site for any reason. Due to the age restrictions, we do not monitor this web site for compliance with any applicable children privacy laws.

**Our Company’s policy toward remarketing and behavioral targeting** :  
We reserve the right to participate with third party advertising partners in remarketing and behavioral targeting programs. These services allow us and our partners to display ads that are likely to be more relevant (such as behavioral or targeted ads that are based on information about your browsing history). This activity is performed by tracking Usage Data and by using cookies to transfer information to the partners that manage the remarketing and behavioral targeting activity.  
These third party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies and other tracking devices to track your activities on this site to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. Tracking may include, but not limited to, the following: first party cookies, third party cookies, anonymous cookies, persistent identifiers, email optin, and search engine keywords. We have no access or control over these cookies and other tracking devices that may be used by third party advertisers, and we have no responsibility or liability for the policies and practices of these sites.  
Trading Concepts inc also uses 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system.  
The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. – Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service.  
AdWords Remarketing (Google) â€“ We reserve the right to participate in AdWords Remarketing which is a Remarketing and Behavioral Targeting service provided by Google Inc. that connects the activity of this site with the Adwords advertising network and the Doubleclick cookie. Information collected: cookie and Usage Data. For the opt-out, visit https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en  
For information in general about Google’s remarketing ad campaigns, and specifically about information regarding DoubleClick cookies and how to control and manage Google’s advertising cookies for these campaigns, visit http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/  
For another Google resource for opting our of Google’s use of cookies, visit http://www.google.com/settings/ads  
For information regarding how Google uses data when you use Google’s partners’ sites or apps, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/  
For anther resource recommended by Google for opting out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies, visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp  
Remarketing through Google Analytics for Display Advertising (Google) â€“ We reserve the right to participate in any and all of the following Google Analytics Advertising Features provided by Google Inc. – Remarketing with Google Analytics, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. These features use first party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) for connecting the tracking activity performed by Google Analytics and its cookies with the Adwords advertising network and the DoubleClick cookie (a third party cookie). Information collected: cookie and Usage Data, including audience data such as age, gender, and interests. For the opt-out, visit https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en You may optout of the Google Analytics service with the Google’s Browser Add-on that’s available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/  
For information in general about Google’s remarketing ad campaigns, and specifically about information regarding DoubleClick cookies and how to control and manage Google’s advertising cookies for these campaigns, visit http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/  
For another Google resource for opting our of Google’s use of cookies, visit http://www.google.com/settings/ads  
For information regarding how Google uses data when you use Google’s partners’ sites or apps, visit http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/  
Custom Audience (Facebook). We reserve the right to participate in Facebook.com’s Custom Audience. A Custom Audience on Facebook.com enables us to display to persons on our email lists targeted, personalized ads when they visit Facebook.com. The ads are based on your shopping experience at our website. No personal information, including your shopping history, is shared with Facebook. The Custom Audience allows us to convert your email address to a unique number that Facebook uses to match to unique numbers that Facebook generates from email addresses of its users. You may optout of participation in our Facebook Custom Audience by sending an email, from the email address you are opting out of, to the email address provided in our contact information below. For your optout to be effective, you must: (i) place the following text in the subject line of the email – “Opting Out of Facebook.com Website Custom Audience Ads”, and (ii) in the body of the email, include your name and email address. We will forward your name and email address to Facebook.com with a request to delete you from all of our Facebook Custom Audience Ads

**Our Companyâ€™s Commitment To Data Security** Services and Websites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of data under our control. While we take all reasonably necessary steps to protect the integrity and security of our data and networks, we cannot guarantee our security measures will prevent â€Â third partyâ€ hackers from illegally accessing our data.

**Revisions** Our Company reserves the right to revise, amend or modify this policy our Terms of Service Agreement and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, by updating this posting.
